Toggle navigation

=======================================================================================================================

    * [Virtual Private Server (Elastic VPS)](https://www.virtbiz.com/dedicated-server/virtual-private-server-vps/ "Virtual Private Server (Elastic VPS)")

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: December 2, 2020

**VIRTBIZ.COM** (“VIRTBIZ”, “Site,” “us” or “we”) is an official website for VIRTBIZ Internet Services, a company providing Internet solutions to the general public.

Your privacy is very important to us. Because we gather certain types of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) from users of our website, we feel you should know how we use the Personal Information that you may voluntarily provide us and the Personal Information that is collected passively through the use of cookies or image tags. The Privacy Policy is a part of the Site’s Terms of Service Agreement, which is binding on all users. Your continued participation indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, maintenance, management and storage of your Personal Information as described below. This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect as long as you are a user of the Site. We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you as a user of the Site immediately upon posting. Therefore, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy often.

##### WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

Generally, you may browse this Site without providing any Personal Information. For certain activities we collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

If you elect to purchase services from us, we will request Personal Information that includes your credit card or other payment information, full name, billing and shipping address, email address and telephone number and any such information that is required to fulfill your order and to communicate with you regarding your order. Sensitive Personal Information such as credit card account numbers will be collected though a secured Internet connection generally via SSL or S-HTTP/HTTPS protocols. We may use your Personal Information, (but not your credit card number) to contact you about future products, services and discounts or to provide information regarding your service with us, unless you tell us otherwise.

##### WHAT IS THIS INFORMATION USED FOR?

We use the information for different purposes depending upon the goods or services being provided. Among other things, these purposes may include the following: making improvements to the content of our Web page; handling orders; delivering products and services; processing payments; processing for other purposes as required by our services; communicating with customers, users and vendors orders, products, services and promotional offers; updating our records and generally maintaining customer, user, and vendor accounts; displaying content; and recommending merchandise and services that might be of interest to our customers and users. We also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our web sites, and enable third parties (such as payment processors, domain name registrars and fraud prevention providers) to carry out technical, logistical or other functions necessary to provide the services we offer. These functions may include the processing of credit-card payments, providing domain name registration services or to provide a transaction fraud threat assessment.

##### WHAT INFORMATION IS SHARED?

We will not sell, exchange, rent, lease or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to other third-party marketers or any such persons that are not associated with us as an advertiser, sponsor, or promotional partner (collectively “Advertisers”) unless it is necessary to 1) conform to regulatory and legal requirements or to comply with legal process, 2) to protect the safety and security of our users, employees, or property, 3) to defend the rights of the Site or the Company, or 4) to enforce the Terms of Service Agreement.  If this process should change in the future, we will update this policy to identify those third parties and provide individuals with appropriate choice (opt-in or opt-out) prior to their data being shared.

##### HOW IS THIS INFORMATION SECURED?

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We conduct the collection, management, maintenance and storage of visitor information in a secure and reasonable manner using acceptable standards of security technology and practices (e.g., electronic security systems -and password protections) to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of Personal Information data. We always use a secured connection for the sale of goods and services but may not use a secured connection for other types of activities. When users transmit Personal Information over an unsecured Internet connection, the Site is not responsible for the security of that information during the transmission stage as your email or registration could be copied or intercepted by unknown third parties. Therefore, you understand, acknowledge, and agree that you transmit certain Personal Information over this Site at your own risk.

##### WHAT INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Generally, any information that you as a customer provide to us may be accessed via our Customer Portal at [https://www.virtbiz.com/customer](https://www.virtbiz.com/customer).    This information may include your name, company name, email address, telephone contact, mailing address and other such information used in the course of business.   The information can be viewed, modified or deleted using the Customer Portal for as long as you remain an active customer with VIRTBIZ.   If you cease to be a customer of VIRTBIZ Internet Services, your information will stay on record with us for up to six (6) months and may be accessed by request.  After that time, your information may be permanently removed from our records.

##### WHAT ARE COOKIES USED FOR?

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, shopping cart contents, and click-thru tracking. The use of cookies is an industry standard and they are currently used on most websites, including this Site. Cookies are a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a website to the hard drive of a user’s computer so that the website administrator may identify the computer and passively track the user’s activities on the website. Image tags work in conjunction with cookies and are small image files that may be located on select pages of our Site.

##### THIRD PARTY RESOURCES

This Site often provides links to third parties’ websites that could be of interest to our users. These websites do not have an affiliation with the Site or Company and may have different privacy policies and business practices than we do. We take no responsibility for such websites, as stated in our Terms of Service Agreement. By use of this Site, you have agreed that you will use the hyperlinks to third party sites at your own risk.

##### REVISIONS AND UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you should have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact our offices in writing at 2000 N Central Expwy, Suite 150, Plano TX 75074, USA.

We're Here For You
------------------

**Phone:** (+01) 972-485-4125  
**FAX:** (+01) 972-485-4140  
  
**Mailing Address:**  
2000 N Central Expressway  
Suite 150  
Plano, Texas 75074  
USA  
  
**Business Office Hours**  
_(Central Time, US)_  
Monday – Thursday: 8am – 5:30pm  
Friday: 8am – 12 (noon)  

© 2024 VIRTBIZ Internet Services
